# Fahmi Ali Husni

♥ Banyuwangi, East Java, Indonesia

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced in web developer, especially in frontend and ui/ux designer. I am currently continuing my 8th semester of Informatics majoring at the University of Muhammadiyah Malang and have a passion for development and technology such as coding, research, and competitive programming.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Frontend Developer Intern

PT Telekomunikasi Indonesia (Persero) Tbk.

July 2023 - Present, Jakarta, Indonesia

## Frontend Developer Intern

PT. Singhasari SEZ - SEAL

July 2022 - December 2022, Malang, Indonesia

- $\bullet$  I am using the Next.JS framework with the Typescript programming language
- Slicing the UI design into the website
- Using the CSS framework with TailwindCSS and UI Components with Flowbite
- State management with Redux
- Using the Fetching API with Axios
- Progress management with Trello

# Frontend Engineering Student - KAMPUS MERDEKA YABB & GoTo

February 2022 - July 2022, Jakarta, Indonesia

- I learned FrontEnd by using ReactIs
- Create Spotify playlists using Spotify Developer with React technology using TypeScript language
- Implementing UI components using react components, such as react bootstrap and implementing styling tailwind css
- Spotify playlist can search songs, create, edit and delete playlists

## **Input Data for Covid-19 Vaccine Student Events**

**UIN Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang** 

September 2

September 2021, Malang, Indonesia

• Vaccine data input

## React JS for Web Development Digital Talent Scholarship - KOMINFO

Digital Talent Scholarship - Komini

- Make a website calculator
- Create a to-do list website

May 2022 - 25 June 2022, Indonesia

## **ORGANIZATION**

#### **Informatics Student Association**

**University of Muhammadiyah Malang Informatics** 

February 2022 - July 2022, Malang, Indonesia

• Information & Communication ( INFOKOM )

### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Muhammadiyah Malang**

**Informatics Engineering** 

• Software Engineering

## **PROJECT**

# Web Development

October 2019 - Present

- WordPress Personal Blog (www.projectfa.com)
- FAL Food Store (https://fal-store.netlify.app/)
- MyPortfolio (https://fahmiali.netlify.app/)
- Web Fullstack Service(http://widduserviceeee.herokuapp.com/)
- Web Design Competetion HimitPens Surabaya (https://botnet-web.netlify.app/)
- Web School Company Profile and Registation Online in Elementary 1 Watukebo (https://sdn1watukebo.sch.id/)
- Calculator Website (https://fahmiali99.github.io/calculator.github.io/)
- Leaf Classification (https://image-klasifikasi-daun.herokuapp.com/)
- Spotify Playlist (https://fal-music.vercel.app/)
- SIPP Kota Batu (https://sipp-dev.vercel.app/)

• Spotify Clone (https://github.com/Fahmiali99/Spotify/)

UI / UX Design October 2019 - Present

- YGuide App Mobile
- Ambul App Mobile
- Booklogia Web App
- Botnet Web App
- Widdu Service Web App

## **SKILLS**

**Programming Language**: JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Java, C++, C, Python, Dart

Framework : Webpack, ReactJs, NextJs, AngularJs, Laravel, Flutter

Styling: Bootstrap, Tailwind Css, Ant Design

UI Component : React Bootstrap, Chakra, Material UI

Design Photo : Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XDVideo

**Editing**: Adobe Premiere Pro, Vegas, Filmora **Audio Editing**: Cubase 5, FL Studio, Pro Tools